e4s.co.uk 2018-10-21

# E4S Privacy Policy

Employment4students.co.uk Limited ("we", "us", "our") respects each individual's right to personal privacy. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") together with our Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to herein, sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect form you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.e4s.co.uk, (the "Website") you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting the Website, you agree to the collection and use of your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

For the purpose of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, ("GDPR") or any subsequent amendment or replacement or supplementary legislation (together "Data Protection Law"), the data controller is Employment4students.co.uk Limited of 2D Station Yard, Thame, Oxfordshire, OX9 3UH, England. 

We confirm that we have a data protection officer ("DPO") who can be contacted as set out at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

  1. **Information we may collect from you.** We only collect data from you in order for you to follow jobs and searches, to apply quickly to job offers, etc. In addition we will collect information in order to contact you with job offers matching your profiles and relevant information about your account. 

We may collect and process data about you based upon one or more of the following lawful basis for processing. 

**Consent** You have the right to withdraw consent at any time. Where consent is the only legal basis for processing, we will cease to process data after consent is withdrawn. 

**Necessary to fulfil a contract** For example: to send your CV to an employer or recruiter for a specific job application. 

**Legitimate Interest** We may process your data when it is in our legitimate interests to do so. 

**Necessary due to a legal obligation** **Information you give us.**

    1. Users do not need to provide any personal data to browse the Website or search for jobs.
    2. You may give us information by filling in forms on the Website for example using a jobseeker or employer account, by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use the Website, apps, subscribe to our Services, create an account, register to job alerts, newsletters or deals, apply for a job on the Website, participate in discussion boards on the Website and enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with the Website. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, personal description and photograph. In each case, the personal data required to use the function or service is indicated.

**Information we collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to the Website, we may collect the following information. 

    3. Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform.
    4. Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from the Website (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

**Information we receive from other sources**

    5. We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. In this case we will have informed you when we collected that data that it may be shared internally and combined with data collected on this Website. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.
  2. **Cookies**
    1. We use cookies on the Website to distinguish you from other users of the Website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the Website and also allows us to improve the Website. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy. 
  3. **Information Usage** We use information held about you in the following ways. 

**Information you give to us.**

    1. Employer, advertiser and job seeker account registration information is stored and used to provide the services available from within that account some of which may result in emails being sent to you, e.g. to follow companies and set up job alerts.
    2. To contact registered jobseekers using the details submitted on the registration form to inform you about jobs related to your relevant search.
    3. To request feedback
    4. To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us.
    5. To provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about.
    6. To notify you about changes to our Services.
    7. To ensure that content from the Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Information we collect about you. We will use this information: 
    8. To administer the Website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. Such data will be used and stored anonymously.
    9. To research Website usage trends and other factors regarding the use and effectiveness of the service provided. Such data will be used and stored anonymously.
    10. To improve the Website to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
    11. To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
    12. As part of our efforts to keep the Website safe and secure.
    13. To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of the Website about goods or services that may interest you or them. When showing you tailored ads or customising your web experience, we will not associate an identifier from cookies or similar technologies with special categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health.
  4. **Your rights** You have the following rights under Data Protection Law: 

\- Access to your personal data.  
\- Rectification or deletion of your personal data.  
\- A restriction on the processing of your personal data.  
\- Object to the processing of your personal data.  
\- A transfer of your personal data (data portability).

You can make a request in relation to any of the above rights, free of charge, by writing to us at the contact address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. We will respond to such queries within 30 days and deal with requests we receive from you, in accordance with the provisions of Data Protection Law. 

**Consent**

    1. You have the right to withdraw your consent to us processing your personal data, at any time, by writing to us at the contact address given at the end of this Privacy Policy.
    2. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at the address given at the end of this Privacy Policy.
    3. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, Users can unsubscribe from any E-newsletter lists at any time by following the "unsubscribe" instructions at the bottom of each E-newsletter and we will remove you from our mailing lists.

**Rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling** You have the right to be free from decisions based solely on automated processing of your personal data, including profiling, that affect you, unless such profiling is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between you and us or you provide your explicit consent. 

**Right to rectification, deletion and data export** Maintaining the accuracy of personal data is the responsibility of job seekers, employers and advertisers, and can be done from within their password protected accounts. We permit you to rectify, delete or export information you have provided to us, subject to the provisions of our Terms and Conditions and the terms set out below. 

    4. Employers and advertisers can delete their accounts by contacting their Account Manager using the contact details provided within their accounts.
    5. Job seekers can delete their accounts using the "close account" function within their account.
    6. You may rectify or export personal data you have provided to us by logging onto the Website and providing additional information where applicable. If you would like to gain access to your account to rectify or export information we have collected as "data controllers," please contact us. We will respond to such queries within 30 days.
    7. We have no direct relationship with any individuals with whom you may interact when using the Website. Any such individual seeking access to, or who would like to rectify, delete or export data which may be stored by us should direct any query to the applicable customer acting as the "data controller" for such information. At the request of our customers, we rectify, delete or export any data placed in their accounts within 30 days.

**Data Retention** We retain personal data for as long as we provide access to the Website to you or your account remains open. However, we may keep some data after your account is closed or you cease using the Website for the purposes set out below. 

    8. After you have closed your account or ceased using the Website for a period of at least 36 months, we usually delete personal data, however we may retain personal data where reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use or Terms and Conditions, or fulfil your request to "unsubscribe" from further messages from us.
    9. We also reserve the right to keep an archival copy of deleted accounts for audit purposes. Deleted accounts will not be accessible to users or third parties on the internet.
    10. We will retain de-personalised information after your account has been closed.
    11. Please note: After you have closed your account or deleted information from your account, any information you have shared with others will remain visible. We do not control data that other users may have copied from the Website. Your profile may continue to be displayed in the services of others (e.g., search engine results) until they refresh their cache.
  5. **Disclosure of your information** We do not disclose your information to third parties or allow them access to it, except in the following circumstances: 

**Information we share with third parties.** We do not share personal information with companies, organisations and individuals outside of Employment4Students.co.uk Ltd unless one of the following applies. 

We may share your information with selected third parties including: 

    1. Any member of our group which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
    2. Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you, such as website hosting or maintenance suppliers and is this is limited to domain administrators, support companies or individuals and sub-processors acting on our behalf.
    3. Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 250 women aged over 25 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, men living in London). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
    4. Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of the Website.

**Information we disclose to third parties.** We may disclose your personal data to third parties: 

    5. If you apply for a job, any personal data you include in your application will be sent to the client who posted that job. Whilst we take precautions to only work with clients who adhere to Data Protection Law, we take no responsibility for the way in which clients use the information you send in your application, or subsequently disclose in correspondence with that client.
    6. In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
    7. If Employment4students.co.uk Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party then your personal data will be passed to that third party as one of the transferred assets. We will publish notice of such an acquisition on the Website.
    8. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and/or any other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, safety, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
    9. Where we share statistical (such as application numbers and Website visit numbers) and demographic data with third parties for advertising, marketing or service provision tendering purposes. None of this information is personal data.
  6. **Posting in Public Areas**
    1. Information posted in our forum, on job adverts or other advertising on the Website is available to anyone on the internet and may be collected by third parties. We have no control over any use of that information by such third parties.
    2. If you post details of third parties in public areas of the Website then it is your sole responsibility to gain consent from those third parties to post such information. We are in no way responsible for obtaining consent from such third parties for your actions.
  7. **Data Storage**
    1. Personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing outside of the EEA.
    2. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In particular, this means that your personal data will only be transferred to a country that provides an adequate level of protection (that is, where the European Commission has determined that a country provides an adequate level of protection) or the recipient is bound by standard contractual clause according to conditions provided by the European Commission ("EU Model Clauses").
    3. The Website is accessible via the internet and may potentially be accessed by anyone around the world. Other users may access the Website from outside the EEA. This means that where you chose to post your data publicly on the Website, it could be accessed from anywhere around the world and therefore a transfer of your data outside of the EEA may be deemed to have occurred. You consent to such transfer of your data for and by way of this purpose.
  8. **Protection and security of your information**
    1. We protect user information with the following security measures: Electronically, the Website is hosted on a secure server, computers are protected with appropriate anti-virus and firewall software, and personal data is accessible only by unique username and password and by administration. It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality of your username and password. We ask you not to share any password with anyone.
    2. We restrict access to personal data to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and the appropriate organizational policies and procedures. such persons may be disciplined or their contract terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.
    3. Although we endeavour to keep information secure, security of both communication and information storage on the internet are beyond our control. We cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedure and security feature to try to prevent unauthorised access.
  9. **Links to other websites**
    1. Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
  10. **Complaints**
    1. We are committed to resolving any problems or disputes as hastily as possible and do so by committing ourselves to the highest standards of customer service and constantly looking to improve both the service we provide and our relationship with you. If problems arise, or you have any complaints about our use of your information please contact us as set out at the end of this Privacy Policy or contact our supervisory authority:  
The Information Commissioner's Office at, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, England ("ICO").
  11. **Age of Users**
    1. This Website is not intended for and shall not be used by anyone under the age of 16.
  12. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**
    1. This Privacy Policy may be changed for any reason, at any time and at our sole discretion. Any amendment to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page to ensure that all users remain informed about the data we collect, how it is used and how it is protected and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy.
    2. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 25th May 2018 and replaces any other Privacy Policy previously applicable from this date.
  13. **Contact**
    1. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or the use of your personal data please call us on 0845 838 0595 or write to: Employment4student.co.uk Limited, 2D Station Yard, Thame, Oxfordshire, OX9 3UH, England;  
or email: dpo@e4s.co.uk
